export const final_mdsp_coaching_phase_3 = [
    {
        choices: ["file", "cold chisel", "none of the above", "hacksaw"],
        correctAnswer: "file",
        question: "A multi pointed hand anything tool used to remove material from metallic and non-metallic work places to match with drawing, shape and size.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["&amp;amp;quot;E&amp;amp;quot;", "&amp;amp;quot;R&amp;amp;quot;", "&amp;amp;quot;B&amp;amp;quot;", "&amp;amp;quot;V&amp;amp;quot;"],
        correctAnswer: "&amp;amp;quot;B&amp;amp;quot;",
        question: "The symbol resinoid bond is:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["medium", "soft", "none of the above", "hard"],
        correctAnswer: "medium",
        question: "as per india standard &amp;amp;quot;M&amp;amp;quot; grade wheel comes under the group:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["swagging", "tapping", "reamer", "peening"],
        correctAnswer: "reamer",
        question: "A side cutting tool used for accurately finishing the straight or tapered holes already drilled or bored",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["shell end mill", "side milling cutter", "semi circular milling cutter", "plain milling cutter"],
        correctAnswer: "shell end mill",
        question: "Mark the cutter which works simultaneously with the up cut and down cut process:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["vise", "pressed", "grip", "clamp"],
        correctAnswer: "vise",
        question: "A notching device, which is used to hold or grip work place, while filing, chipping or any other bench work or while machining or drilling them.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["the job will not rotate", "the job will be out of round", "the job will be oversize", "the job will be thrown out"],
        correctAnswer: "the job will be out of round",
        question: "What happens if the job is loosely fitted between centers in cylindrical grindings?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["hardness of bond", "grain size", "kind of abrasive", "structure"],
        correctAnswer: "hardness of bond",
        question: "The grade of grinding wheel depends upon&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;                                    ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["vernier caliper", "steel rule", "micrometer", "all of the above"],
        correctAnswer: "all of the above",
        question: "The common measuring tools are:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["on the circumstances", "relieve cutters are not regrounded", "on the flank", "on the side faces"],
        correctAnswer: "on the flank",
        question: "Where the relieve cutter are regrounded?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["shellac", "silicon", "rubber", "vitrified"],
        correctAnswer: "vitrified",
        question: "Which kind of bond is commonly used?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["rubber", "none of the above", "shellac", "silicate"],
        correctAnswer: "silicate",
        question: "which bond is suitable in wet grinding?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["medium grain", "fine grain", "coarse grain", "very fine grain"],
        correctAnswer: "medium grain",
        question: "As per india standard the grain size 46 comes under the group:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["should be easy to read", "should be wear resistance", "all of the above", "should be easy to handle"],
        correctAnswer: "all of the above",
        question: "The good quality of a measuring tool",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["wheel is hard", "wheel speed is too fast", "a and b both", "grain size is too fine"],
        correctAnswer: "a and b both",
        question: "which of the following is used in cleaning the gage blocks before and after use?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["make the sides of wheel parallel", "none of the above", "make the outside diameter concentric with the bore", "equalize the weight in every portion the wheel"],
        correctAnswer: "equalize the weight in every portion the wheel",
        question: "Balancing of grinding wheel is done to:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["universal cylindrical grinding machine", "internal grinding machine", "centerless grinding machine", "plain cylindrical grinding machine"],
        correctAnswer: "universal cylindrical grinding machine",
        question: "The internal and external taper on cylindrical jobs are ground in:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["kind of bond", "structure", "kind of abrasive", "grain size"],
        correctAnswer: "structure",
        question: "The grinding wheel is marked as 51A 46L 5V 23, out of these 5 means:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["upsetting", "peening", "bending", "swaging"],
        correctAnswer: "peening",
        question: "It is an operation in stretching or spreading over the metal by means of the plane of the hammer",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["corrundum", "aluminum oxide", "silicon carbide", "combination of a and b"],
        correctAnswer: "silicon carbide",
        question: "A grinding wheel which has got the marking &amp;amp;quot;C&amp;amp;quot; is made with the abrasive?",
        topic: "NA"
    },

]